[ Charlie ]
Would you describe this piece
as more savory or succulent?
Well, it's definitely way
too overcooked to be succulent.
But it's still pretty delicious.
It's still savory, right?
Mm-hmm.
What if we soaked it in beer?
Do you think that would help
it regain its succulence?
Like a beer rub?
Mm-hmm.
That's actually really smart.
Mac, grab us some beers.
Bite my bird.
What are you eating?
Dude, Dee and I cooked
up a great steak.
Frank's got this whole fridge
full of these delicious meats
that I've been stealing.
You guys want
to try some of this?
Someone who sweats
as much as you
should not work with food.
Charlie!
You son of a bitch!
I told you to stay away
from my meat! Spit it out!
Come on, man.
Spit it!
Spit it out! Now!
You too! Spit!
Come on.
Right there.
- Why are you
such a selfish jerk?
- Hey!
I killed the deer,
I should get to eat it.
That's the natural order.
- Wait. You shot a deer?
- That's right. Ten-point buck.
[ Imitates Rifle Firing ]
Right between its soulful
little eyes.
- Since when do you hunt, bro?
- Since always.
I'm a great hunter.
How does hunting
a defenseless creature
make you a good hunter?
You should go after something
that could defend itself.
Yeah.
You know, a really great hunter
would go after something
that could hunt him back.
Oh!
Like a man.
- Hell, yeah, dude. A man?
- Don't even joke
about hunting no man.
Who's joking?
I'm not joking.
No.
I think that hunting a man
would be the only true test
of a good hunter.
Oh, yeah? I was hunted once.
I just came back from 'Nam.
I was hitching through Oregon,
and some cop started
harassing me.
Next thing you know,
I had a whole army of cops
chasing me through the woods!
I had to take 'em all out.
It was a bloodbath.
That's Rambo, dude.
- What?
- You just described
the plot of Rambo.
That's from the first one.
It's First Blood.
I think you're confusing
your life with Rambo.
Not the first time
you've described your life in
the way of John Rambo's life.
You know what? It's actually
making me think I could get
on board with a manhunt.
Really? Me too, dude.
I'm just throwing
that out there.
No! You do not
go on a manhunt.
[ Laughs ]
Screw you.
Yeah.
[ Charlie ]
Try that one.
[ Dee ] This one?
Mm-hmm. And get a little bit
of the sauce with it.
I don't have any sauce left.
It's the natural juices, by the
way. It's not an actual sauce.
It's so good.
Oh, my God. Good job.
Mm-hmm.
I can't believe that dick hole,
though, put the lock
on the refrigerator.
What a son of a bitch.
That wasn't cool.
You know what though? At least
he forgot about this piece.
That dumb ass.
But did you do something
different though?
'Cause it's so good this time.
I barely cooked it.
Really?
I'm talking like not at all.
No kidding?
What I did, I slapped it on
the radiator for a minute.
That's pretty gross.
And that warmed it.
No, but it's clean enough.
It's so good. I don't care.
Okay, good.
Well, well, well,
what have we here?
Looks like you two
have been enjoying my meat!
Yes. We have been,
you fascist meat hog.
Yeah!
Hey, Frankie.
♪ Sharing, it's a rule now ♪
[ Blows Raspberry ]
Well, I'm glad
you enjoyed yourselves.
Maybe we should open up
a bottle of dessert wine.
A nice port
that would complement...
what you have just eaten.
By the way, you know what
you've just eaten, right?
Was it venison?
You wish it was venison!
Was it a horse?
Horse?
That which
you have just eaten,
that which your teeth
have just torn apart,
your taste buds
have savored,
that was human meat.
[ Scoffs ]
[ Laughs ]
Yeah, okay.
You're so stupid.
You're so stupid!
Thank you for
the human meat, Frank.
Thank you for our human meat.
It was delicious.
You're welcome.
I knew you were gonna steal
from me again.
You're stupid.
That's why I put
a lock on the fridge.
Yeah.
And only left one piece
of meat out.
Mm-hmm, okay.
Human meat.
All right, where'd you get
the human meat from, Frank?
I got a guy.
You got a guy?
You got a human meat guy?
I got a guy for
everything, Charlie.
You're so full of shit.
Oh, yeah, Deandra?
You think I'm full of shit?
Mm-hmm.
Well, you enjoy
yourselves now.
Thank you.
I am glad you had
a good time eating...
Thank you.
human meat.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Door Opens ]
[ Door Closes ]
That wasn't human
meat though, was it?
No!
Hey-o!
Dennis, I did it!
It took me all day,
but I finally finished the list
of 10 people that would be
perfect to hunt.
Great. And I totally
respect your opinion, but
I've already made a decision.
That's the complete opposite
of respecting my opinion.
Hey, don't I know it.
Check it out, bro.
Hey. Dennis,
are you sure
Dee is coming?
Yeah, yeah, she's coming.
She just wants to look great
for your big date.
Cricket, bro?
Are you serious?
Yeah, man. He's perfect.
You don't believe me?
Check it out. Cricket, come
out here for a second, please.
Yeah.
Just stand before us here.
Now check out his legs.
See how they've almost healed?
They're, like, pretty much
back to perfect.
Yeah.
And check out his cane.
It looks like he's whittled it
into some sort
of defensive tool.
Wow.
Bet that makes you
quite formidable, huh?
Okay, what's
going on here? Huh?
Where's Dee?
Admit it, Mac.
He's perfect.
Yeah. Yeah,
he'll do just fine.
Oh, God.
Oh, God. I knew you
were up to something.
You're gonna harvest my organs,
aren't you? Yeah.
Hey, relax.
You're gonna probe--
Cricket, relax.
Relax. Take it easy.
You don't want to be all nervous
and sweaty when Dee gets here.
So she is coming?
Mm-hmm.
Okay. Okay.
For a second there, I
thought you guys were gonna
do something terrible to me.
Yeah, we are.
She's not coming.
No. We're gonna hunt you.
- What?
- We are going to
hunt you, Cricket.
Why?
I'd spend less time asking
questions and more time running.
Yeah.
What happens if--
if I get caught?
Ooh, don't get caught!
Don't get caught.
Whoa! There he goes.
And the hunt begins.
Indeed. Indeed.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
This is gonna be fun.
What do you suppose
is gonna happen
when we do catch him?
I suppose we do something
tea bag related.
Mmm.
[ Knocking ]
Dee! You're home.
Thank God. Okay, let's talk.
Let's have a quick conversation.
What do you think?
I couldn't sleep last night.
Could you?
No.
And I'll tell you why.
Yesterday.
- What's going on?
- Oh, my God, Charlie.
I didn't want to say anything.
But I'm thinking there's
something strange going on
with this meat situation.
Yes! Now I know it's crazy,
the idea of Frank
feeding us human meat.
Yes!
But I've been trying to
disprove it. I absolutely can't.
You can't do it, can you?
Let's talk the taste.
The taste, Charlie.
The taste. I can't get
the taste out of my mouth!
You can't get it out, right?
Absolutely not.
Have you tried all sorts
of other meats? Like deli meats
and sandwich meats?
Absolutely!
Did you go crazy just licking
everything in your apartment?
Like your shoe?
I even licked the cat's fanny.
Like nothing's working, right?
Maybe it's a trick, okay?
Maybe he went and
got some weird exotic meat
that we wouldn't think to try.
It's not like regular
grocery store kind of meat.
Not meat from a grocery store.
It's like he got it
from some weird place.
Well, let's think here.
Let's put our heads together.
Where could Frank go
to get mysterious meat?
[ Dee ]
This is the place, huh?
This is what we're looking for.
Just start grabbing
as much stuff as you can.
We'll take that big brown
mound, and the curly stuff.
Then this thing that looks
like a blanket, definitely.
Try some of that.
Oh, oh, oh!
What about a monkey? Monkeys
are like nature's humans.
I doubt they have monkey,
Charlie.
People eat monkey, Dee.
They ate it in Temple of Doom.
You ever see that?
Hey.
We got monkey.
Oh. Well, would you
look at that? Great.
One monkey also
then, please.
[ Laughs ]
Yeah, baby!
This hunt is gonna be
so awesome, dude!
Yeah, bro!
This is what it must feel like
before you go into battle!
Oh, my God.
I know, man. I'm so excited.
Feel my nips.
Holy smokes!
They're super hard, right?
Whoo! You could cut glass
with these bad boys.
- I know, right?
- What the hell are you doing?
I'm feeling his nips,
Frank.
I am so excited for this hunt
my nips are doing stuff they've
never done before. Feel 'em.
- What hunt?
- We're gonna hunt Cricket.
I thought we went
over this already.
You do not hunt a man!
Don't bring me down.
Not right now.
Not while my nips are like this.
You know, you hunt a man,
he could snap like a twig.
Next thing you know,
he's up at night, he's burning
down a village in 'Nam,
he's killing
everything that moves,
everything that lives!
You're talking
about Rambo again.
Oh, no. That happened to me.
You're thinking of John Rambo's
life every time you--
I'm not. This happened to me.
- That never happened
to you, Frank.
- It happened to me, Mac.
You're confusing your life
with Rambo again.
No! No, Charlie!
This is not right.
I still have the craving.
I have it too.
I have it even worse
than before I think.
Something really weird
is happening to me.
Frank fed us human meat
and we got the hunger.
The hunger?
That's how you become
a cannibal, Dee. You get one
taste of delicious human meat,
none of this stuff ever
satisfies you ever again.
Now I just think that
you're overreacting, okay?
Oh, really?
Yeah, that's stupid.
Is that stupid?
Oh, I'm sorry, Dee!
Well, then I guess Jaws IV
is stupid, okay, because
that's the exact same plot!
Okay! All right, calm down!
Before you start accusing us of
becoming cannibals or sharks...
or whatever it is
you're trying to say,
I think we need to find out
if what we ate
was actually human.
No shit.
That's what we've been doing.
I ate a-- [ Bleeps ]
monkey, Dee!
You don't understand me.
I think we need to try
a piece of human flesh.
Oh, God.
Just to make sure.
That's the only way.
Right?
How we gonna do this?
The morgue? Hear me out.
It's a dead body--
Sold.
You don't even have to tell me.
That's where you find
dead bodies.
It's a great idea, right?
And we'll only have
a tiny little bit.
And then we'll know.
We'll know for sure.
We'll be off the hook.
I got a hot plate.
I'm gonna get some beers.
- Any sign of him?
- No.
But word on the street is he's
out here begging most Saturdays.
He'll be here.
Don't worry about it.
God, hunting is awesome, Dennis!
Yeah.
You get to wear sweet clothes
and get wasted all day.
It's just like our normal lives,
except at the end of it,
we get to put our nuts
in some dude's mouth.
Uh, yeah.
Actually, I wanted to talk
to you about that aspect of it.
What's up?
You're not happy with the plan?
Look, dude.
We've been tea bagging
Cricket since high school.
Yeah!
I feel like we need
to make some progress.
I think we should give him
a gorilla mask.
What's a gorilla mask?
You put something sticky
all over his face. And then
sprinkle it with shaved pubes.
Mmm, no, I don't like it.
What? What's not to like?
Cricket with a face full
of pubes? Hilarious.
But where are we supposed
to get that many pubes, man?
We shave!
That's gonna be a problem.
I laser. It's like
a turtle shell down there.
What?
Yeah. Look, man. Classics
are classics for a reason, okay?
Why go and mess with that?
Well, it's called
progress, Dennis.
I don't want to make progress!
We're sticking with
the tea bagging!
But tea bagging
doesn't even leave a mark!
Well, fine!
I'll dip my nuts in ink or
something and then put it in
his mouth! That make you happy?
Well-- Yeah, actually.
I think that's
a pretty good idea.
- It leaves a mark all over him.
- Holy shit. I'm glad
we just thought of it.
So we can dunk him down
and, like-- Whoo!
Cheers, man.
Glad we went through that.
We're free thinking
outside the box.
Cricket!
Get him!
Get him, get him,
get him, get him!
Okay, how did his legs
just do that?
I'm not doing that, Dennis.
No. That was
incredibly dangerous.
Let's go polish off that case.
Did not know
he was capable of that.
Yo.
Okay.
[ Clears Throat ]
Hi.
Sorry to bug you here.
How-- How are you?
I'm good.
We're two friends of--
of one of the dead people
that you have in there.
Very close friends. Uh--
[ Stammers ]
And we wanted to--
Spend some time maybe.
We wanted to say good-bye.
Say good-bye to her,
him, or--
To him, I--
He had a--
A long life that was good.
What's the hot plate for?
The hot--
The hot plate is because--
Our friend was a--
He was a chef--
A chef who cooked--
Of small plates
of things.
Many small items
on a hot plate.
He mostly just heated it up.
And we thought maybe if he saw
or was near the hot plate
one more time--
It would make him feel--
Right, right, right, right.
Look, spare me the act.
I'll give you guys the same deal
I give everyone else.
50 bucks gets you 10 minutes
alone with the bodies.
What?
What is he talking about?
I gotta say though,
I ain't never seen a guy
and a girl...
bang one of these stiffs
at the same time.
[ Clicks Teeth ]
Are you kidding me, guy?
Okay, you've got
the wrong idea.
You've got
the wrong idea about us.
That's really gross.
We were gonna come in
and have a bite of--
Uh-uh--
I don't judge you guys.
It's cool.
I like yogurt up my ass and
a Popsicle stick in my mouth.
Oh, my God, man! You know what?
Let's just give this guy
his 50 bucks!
Whatever, man! You're the
one with the hot plate.
That is--
- Weirdo.
- That is much worse.
Okay, yeah.
I'm the weirdo says the guy
with the yogurt up his ass.
Holy shit.
Ooh, these are dead bodies.
Two dead guys.
This is the real deal here.
I don't think
I can eat this guy.
No. I don't think I can, right?
What is that?
I don't know.
It's not because
he's black though, right?
What?
Okay.
Well, no. I just
don't think so. No.
It's because he's dead,
right?
It's because he's dead.
Okay, good, good, good.
That's why not.
[ Exhales Sharply ]
Now I got a question for you.
Mm-hmm.
Is it racist
if we don't eat this guy?
Well, shit, Charlie.
Now it is.
I'm sorry, Dee. I just--
The white guy looks better
to me for some reason.
He looks so much better.
What is that?
You know what it is? Generally,
I don't eat dark meat.
No, I prefer the white meat.
I always have.
Yeah. So it's not that guy.
It's this guy.
The problem is I'm gonna
have a really hard time...
if we're both cannibals
and we're racists.
We're not, Dee!
I just want to make sure--
Cannibalism? Racism, Dee?
That's not for us.
You know, those are the
decisions that are best left
to the suits in Washington.
Okay? We're just here
to eat some dude.
Well, you lost me
with Washington.
But the rest I agree with.
So let's eat a piece
of this white guy.
Let's get him.
I don't think I can do it.
No, me neither.
No. Hey, the good news is
that means we're not racist.
Yeah, I guess so.
Okay, okay, okay.
[ Panting ]
I made it!
I'm fast as lightning.
I beat you, bitches.
[ Panting Continues ]
Hey, street rat.
[ Gasps ]
Don't--
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm not here to kill you.
I'm here to help you turn
the tables on Mac and Dennis.
What do you mean?
I want to show those bastards
it ain't okay to hunt humans!
Yeah?
They drew first blood,
not you.
They what?
They drew first blood!
What is that?
Is that, uh--
Is that Rambo?
No, I made that up.
No, no, no.
Yeah, that's Rambo.
You want me
to help you or not?
Yes. Yes.
All right.
Come on. Let's go.
[ Laughs ]
Holy shit.
[ Door Opens ]
Holy shit, dude. Holy shit!
"Tag! You're it!" And a knife?
What the hell is this, man?
Why you laughing?
Stop laughing, dude.
This is serious shit.
Yeah?
What? Oh, my God.
Are you kidding me?
You gorilla masked me?
Yes! Bro, you gotta admit,
that is so much more awesome
than tea bagging!
Oh, yeah?
Take a look at your mouth.
You tell me.
[ Laughs ]
You put your balls in my mouth
while I was sleeping?
- Yeah, man. Twice.
- That's rape!
That is borderline rape!
- You got a lot of pubic hair.
- Well, not anymore.
Yeah, I guess not. Jesus, man,
what's with the note?
What's with the theatrics?
- No, I didn't leave it.
I thought you left it.
- So it was Cricket!
- Oh, shit!
- Okay, Cricket got to us.
- Goddamn it! He got to us.
- The good news is
the gorilla mask,
the purple tea bag,
both totally viable
options, right?
The bad news is it looks
like Cricket's finally snapped.
We may have pushed him
too far, Dennis. What do
you think he's gonna do?
We need to get to him first.
We need to set a trap.
Yeah. And how do you
catch a Cricket?
With a giant bird.
Dee, will you calm down.
You're eating that cheesesteak
like some kind of giant bird,
you know?
I can't help it, Charlie.
I got an insatiable hunger.
I know what the hunger is, Dee!
Don't start telling me about
the hunger. I'm feeling it good!
Let's just go back
to the morgue, okay?
Because this is shit.
No, that place is terrible.
I can't go back there.
Look, Dee, we're cannibals now!
I mean, it's pretty
obvious to me!
It's starting to look
that way, isn't it?
It's a fact. That's what it is.
Look, if we don't feed the
hunger, we could die from it.
It's not our fault. It's nature.
That's nature.
That's what happens.
People die from the hunger.
Oh, my God.
All the time that happens.
We don't want that to happen.
I don't want it to happen to me.
You want it to happen to you?
No. I don't want it to happen
to me. But I'm not going
back to that morgue.
We gotta do something about it.
I know.
Oh, Charlie.
I wanted to eat
that lady so bad.
I did too!
We're gonna have to do it!
We're gonna have to find
a living human being.
Because it's dead meat.
And dead meat's bad meat.
No, not the morgue.
What?
I'm with you on this.
And this thing.
I've never wanted that before.
I want it now.
But I want it now.
We gotta find a guy,
and we gotta kill that guy,
and we gotta eat it.
Somebody a little
rotund maybe.
Yeah.
Somebody--
That nobody'll start
asking questions about--
Oh, right.
If he's missing.
When we do that,
we don't want any questions.
We don't want to get caught.
Someone no one in the world
could ever care about!
[ Man ] Spare change?
Ow! Goddamn, dude!
These are not coming off.
Seriously.
Oh, no.
They're not going to.
I used airplane glue, bro.
That's gonna be your look
for a while.
Now run me through how
we're gonna do this with Dee.
I'll talk her into it.
Dee. Ah, great.
We need to use you as bait
for our Cricket trap.
What in the hell
is going on here?
Who is this?
No, no. We don't want
to know his name.
Go away!
No, wait, wait! Dee, what--
Oh, my God, no!
What are we doing?
What?
You know what, kid?
You gotta get outta here, man.
It's not safe for you.
Dee, we can't do this!
No, no. Charlie, listen to me.
Listen to me good.
If we don't eat this kid,
we are gonna die.
Oh, my God!
I want to eat him as much
as you want to eat him!
- But it's wrong to do it!
- No, it's not! No, come--
- Go back to the streets!
- So you were gonna eat
that kid--
- You don't have the hunger.
- We don't give a shit
about any of this.
Dee, Cricket trap,
bait, you?
Hmm?
Hello? Hey, Frank.
Frank?
Speaker? Yeah, hold on.
[ Phone Beeps ]
Is Dennis with you?
Uh, yeah.
Good.
Mac and Dennis, prepare
to be burned alive.
[ Frank Laughs ]
This is the point
where I would normally
burn you alive.
But I just did it
to prove a point.
And I think I made my point.
Frank. Hey, Frank.
Hey, Frank.
Hey, Frankie.
Good to see you.
Good to see you, man.
Look. Can you get us some
more of that human meat?
Bodies, please.
Are you still going on
about the meat?
I didn't feed you human meat.
It was a raccoon!
Huh?
What?
You ate raccoon meat!
I told you it was people...
because I wanted
to freak you out because
you're stealing my food.
No. No, no.
No, no.
Then why am I always hungry?
And I have stomach pains.
It hurts.
And nothing satisfies
my hunger.
You probably got a tapeworm.
That coon meat is lousy
with parasites.
Okay. Are we done here?
Because we are bored as shit.
No, no, no, no, no.
Not yet.
Get ready for a mouthful...
of strawberry blond-haired
covered balls.
[ Chuckles ]
Frank, grab 'em.
We're not doing that.
Get out.
What do you mean
we're not doing it?
I lied.
What?
What is it with you people?
You guys are always touching
each other's nipples,
putting your balls
in each other's mouths.
It's fun.
It's funny.
I just don't understand
your generation.
[ Laughs ]
Raccoon meat!
Bullshit!
What?
That was human meat
and I know it!
Look! I don't give a shit
what you think.
Oh, really?
I'm gonna chop off a piece
of that fat little calf muscle
of yours, Frank,
and I'm gonna eat it!
Oh, yes.
- We're gonna put it on
the hot plate, right?
- Yes, Charlie. Get him!
- Oh! You can't run from me!
- Get him! Get him!
And I guess the hunt
is on once again.
Indeed it is.
-They're gonna have so much fun.
-Oh, those two are gonna
have a blast, huh?
So I guess the only thing
that's left is to figure out
what to do with Mr. Cricket.
Yeah. Oh, what to do,
what to do.
I guess it's just us.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah.
It's just you
and us...
[ Crunching Food ]
and a couple pairs
of sour, sweaty balls.
[ Voices Speaking Backwards ]